<resources>
    <!-- English Language -->
    <string name="app_name">Java Tutorial</string>
    <string name="java_tutorial">Java Tutorial</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="intro1">
        <font size="30"><b>Java Introduction\n\n\n</b></font>
        <font size="18"><b>What is Java?\n\n</b></font>
        <font size="14">\t\tJava is a widely used object-oriented programming language and software platform that runs on billions of devices. Its syntax is based on C and C++ languages and offers portability. Invented in 1991 by James Gosling, Java aims to "write once, run anywhere." Unlike JavaScript, Java code requires compilation and can be run anywhere. Over the past two decades, Java has remained the most popular language for application software development, surpassing languages like Python, Ruby, PHP, Swift, and C++.\n\n\n\nSource : https://www.ibm.com/topics/java</font>
    </string>
    <string name="intro2">
        <font size="18"><b>How Java works\n\n</b></font>
        <font size="14">\t\tJava is a popular technology for enterprise application development, consisting of a programming language and a software platform. To create an application, download the Java Development Kit (JDK) for Windows, macOS, and Linux. Java bytecode is written in the Java programming language and executed by a compiler on a Java Virtual Machine (JVM). The Java software platform includes the JVM, Java API, and a development environment.\n\n\n\nSource : https://www.ibm.com/topics/java</font>
    </string>
    <string name="intro3">
        <font size="18"><b>Why Java matters\n\n</b></font>
        <font size="14">\t\tJava is a widely used language in enterprise application development, serving as the foundation for Android operating systems, machine learning, and data science applications. Its robustness, ease of use, cross-platform capabilities, and security make it a popular choice for internet solutions. Java application servers, web containers for Java components, XML, and web services, provide a stable deployment environment for enterprise applications, offering transaction management, security, clustering, performance, availability, connectivity, and scalability.\n\n\n\nSource : https://www.ibm.com/topics/java</font>
    </string>
</resources>